<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Merve Bozkir</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Merve Bozkir</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Service Testing with Karate DSL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/more-testing-with-karate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/more-testing-with-karate/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the previous article, we talked about creating a project with Karate and created a small test. Now, let&amp;rsquo;s try to create some more detailed test examples.
Testing For our first example, let&amp;rsquo;s look at API examples on GitHub. On the opened page, under the Public APIs heading, we can click on the Animals option or scroll down to reach the same heading.
I selected the IUCN Red List of Threatened Species example from the Animals API examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Karate DSL? How to Create a Project and Perform Web Service Testing?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/what-is-karate-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/what-is-karate-testing/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hello everyone, in this article, I will talk about the use of Karate. And no it&amp;rsquo;s NOT THE Karate. 😅
First, let&amp;rsquo;s briefly introduce Karate. Karate is an open-source test tool created by Peter Thomas in 2017. With Karate, it is possible to perform manual testing, automation testing, and performance testing.
We can list its basic features as follows:
You do not need to know any programming language to use the Karate tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Service Testing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/web-service-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/web-service-testing/</guid>
      <description>What is a Web Service? The most basic definition of a web service is the standard protocols (HTTP or HTTPS) used for communication between systems. This communication is mostly centered around XML and JSON.
Briefly, XML (Extensible Markup Language) is a language that enables the creation of easily readable documents, known in Turkish as Genişletilebilir İşaretleme Dili.
JSON (JavaScript Object Notation), which translates to JavaScript Nesne Notasyonu in Turkish, is a more flexible language compared to XML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile and Waterfall Methods in Software World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/agile-and-waterfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/agile-and-waterfall/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One of the most used concepts in the software world is SDLC (Software Development Life Cycle). So, what is SDLC? Briefly, it is the processes that include the development, design, and testing of a product.
Understanding software development processes is as important for a test engineer as test quality, types, and test tools. In this article, I tried to briefly convey the most common SDLC processes, Agile and Waterfall modeling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
